I've got a bottle, where does it go?
我有一個瓶子，它去哪兒了？
It's made of plastic, where does it go?
它是塑料做的，去哪兒了？
I've got a bottle, where does it go?
我有一個瓶子，它去哪兒了？
Let's sort out all the trash!
讓我們把所有的垃圾都清理掉！
The plastic goes in the plastic bin.
塑料進入塑料箱。
Let's sort out all the trash!
讓我們把所有的垃圾都清理掉！
I've got a box, oh, where does it go?
我有一個盒子，哦，它去哪兒了？
It's made of cardboard, where does it go?
它是用紙板做的，它去哪兒了？
I've got a box, oh, where does it go?
我有一個盒子，哦，它去哪兒了？
Let's sort out all the trash!
讓我們把所有的垃圾都清理掉！
The cardboard goes in the cardboard bin.
紙板進入紙板箱。
Let's sort out all the trash!
讓我們把所有的垃圾都清理掉！
I've got a can, oh, where does it go?
我有一個罐頭，哦，它去哪兒了？
It's made of metal, where does it go?
它是金屬做的，它去哪兒了？
I've got a can, oh, where does it go?
我有一個罐頭，哦，它去哪兒了？
Let's sort out all the trash!
讓我們把所有的垃圾都清理掉！
The metal goes in the metal bin.
金屬進入金屬箱。
Let's sort out all the trash!
讓我們把所有的垃圾都清理掉！
I've got a jar, oh, where does it go?
我有一個罐子，哦，它去哪兒了？
It's made of glass, so where does it go?
它是由玻璃製成的，那麼它去哪裡了？
I've got a jar, oh, where does it go?
我有一個罐子，哦，它去哪兒了？
Let's sort out all the trash!
讓我們把所有的垃圾都清理掉！
The glass things go in the glass bin.
玻璃東西放在玻璃箱裡。
Let's sort out all the trash!
讓我們把所有的垃圾都清理掉！
I've got an apple core, where does it go?
我有一個蘋果核，它去哪兒了？
It's leftover food, so where does it go?
剩飯剩菜了，去哪了？
I've got an apple core, where does it go?
我有一個蘋果核，它去哪兒了？
Let's sort out all the trash!!!
讓我們把所有的垃圾都清理掉！！！
The food scraps go in the compost bin.
食物殘渣進入堆肥箱。
Let's sort out all the trash!
讓我們把所有的垃圾都清理掉！
Sorting out trash is good for the earth.
整理垃圾對地球有好處。
Let's sort out all the trash!
讓我們把所有的垃圾都清理掉！